[{"answer": "It's a tough go for this guy, yes.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What do you make of this?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "You tell me.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Can you survive if you don't have credibility and don't have trust in the public office?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know how you would get up and start to represent your constituents with no credibility and no trust.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "He should go, you think?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Neither event is pretty, particular all the photos out there.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Is it the lying that has made it a completely unsurvivable scandal?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "It's no fun.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "When you go through it though, when you are the subject of headlines like this, what's it like?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "So, actually, honesty, when you're caught, is the best way with all these things?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Would that formula you deployed then for G.E., would that work for America as -- if you viewed it as a corporation?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Out-innovating them is the way to beat China.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Or do you think the actual answer with China is to be more competitive by giving them what they need?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "That is a great question.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Why aren't there more Steve Jobses being created in America?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I want to come back and ask you how we get the uncertainty out of the game.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What are the rules?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "With the right policies, certainly do.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Do you share his faith, Jack?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "So many things can be attributed to what caused the problem, but certainly lots of money available too easy.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What went so catastrophically wrong that meant that we had this terrible financial crisis?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "No, I don't think it's so much greed.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Is that because greed kicks in?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Boy, that's a hard one.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Who was most to blame?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I would have cleaned out anybody in the mortgage business who put faulty mortgages together.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "I mean, who were the main culprits here from a business perspective?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I'm not -- I'm not qualified to pick that, whether that's true or not.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Should some of these people have gone to jail?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Look, there's a culture in Wall Street, I own (INAUDIBLE) -- which is one of the worst moments in my life.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "If you'd been running Goldman Sachs, would you have allowed the multimillion dollar bonuses to be paid out after the bailout for the next few years?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "All he cared about.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "He said, this won't hurt my bonus, will it?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Well, I mean --", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Should they have done it?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "But it's interesting that you even hesitate, because you've been a big supporter previously, I'll grant you that, of allowing people to be paid what they should get in the marketplace.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "So I'm not going to get drabbed into that one, OK?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Seems to be.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "It's wrong, isn't it?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I wouldn't support her for president.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "When she says something like that, does it worry you she might have her finger on the nuclear trigger within a couple years?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I just wouldn't support her for president.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "You think she'd be dangerous?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I don't think she has the gravitas or the international depth or a lot of things.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, people follow her.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "And you think it's because of that she's getting support?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, this is a great question, because if you asked me that a month ago, I would have said, well, Mitt Romney might be best guy, et cetera -- the most obvious guy.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Do you see anybody emerging on the Republican side who is the kind of ladder that you're looking for?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "I mean, you're a Republican, right?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "I'm going to find out over the next 15 months -- hopefully, the next six to nine months because they're going to pick somebody in the primary.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "But in your heart, do you think he can beat someone like Obama?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "He likes what he says.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Why do you think he's doing that?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "They ought to talk about them.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "When you look at countries like China, India, Brazil, so on, these emerging superpowers, economic powerhouses, how should America deal with this threat, which they've never had to face before?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Out innovate them, which we can do, which we do all the time.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "What is the right way to deal with China?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Excite me.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Do they scare you or excite you, the Chinese?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I don't like the old part of it.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "How do you feel about being a cute old dude, Jack?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Hide them.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "The trick is not to let anybody see then, right?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Something like that.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "That true?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "For a kid from Salem that went through a 50 dollar a semester college, a hell of a country, huh.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Not bad, is it?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Does money make you happy?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "We're manufacturing lots of great -- we don't want to manufacture t-shirts.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Why isn't it recognizing that this is probably the big problem?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "We are.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What about, for example, very heavy big plant machinery and ship it to China, where they really need it?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "We're doing tons of it.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Are we doing enough?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "ELCH: We're seeing it.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Isn't that where you could see real growth?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Of course we do.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Would you like to se more companies like that?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Yes, one of the solutions is that.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Is that one of the answers, one of the solutions?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Yes, I think we are.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Are we getting enough of this ideology at the moment in America?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Well, it's a -- they do it their way.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What's your experience of doing business with the Chinese?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Warren will never understand that, nor will others.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Were you surprised by the Warren Buffett affair recently, when his top guy had to leave in what were pretty unethical circumstances?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Warren runs a very decentralized company.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "Were you surprised that he allowed it to happen?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "They did go off for Warren.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Do you think if you'd been in his shoes and a top, top executive, running the show for you comes to you and says what that guy said to Warren Buffett, wouldn't alarm bells go off?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "It was my big moment in the sun, I'll tell you.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Do you enjoy your acting?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "One of them.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Best businessman in the world right now?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Not one.", "docId": "110608pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "Who's been to you the most inspirational over all the years, all the business people you've met?", "qSentId": 709}]